<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TheStudentSaver</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>


    <!-- Home screen text -->

    <!-- Welcome Card -->

    <string name="welcome_card_title"> Welcome Back!</string>
    <string name="welcome_card_description">This is StudentSaver! The app to help get you great deals.</string>


    <!-- Discount Page Text -->
    <string name="DiscountCode">Discount Code</string>
    <string name="clientName">Client Name</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>

    <!-- Notification Texts -->
    <string name="Mcdonalds">Enjoy a free Cheeseburger, Mayo Chicken or McFlurry Original® when you order an Extra Value or Wrap Meal at McDonalds</string>
    <string name="TopShop">Enjoy 10% Student Discount when you shop with Topshop in-store</string>
    <string name="Accessorize">Enjoy up to 30% Off sale items + an extra 10% Off when you shop with Accessorize in-store.</string>
    <string name="AnnSummers">Enjoy 10% Student Discount when you shop with Ann Summers in-store.</string>
    <string name="Schuh">Enjoy 10% Student Discount when you shop with Schuh in-store.</string>
    <string name="Select">Enjoy 20% Student Discount when you shop with Select in-store.</string>
    <string name="USC">Enjoy 10% Student Discount when you shop with USC in-store.</string>
    <string name="Burton">Enjoy 10% Student Discount when you shop with Burton in-store.</string>
    <string name="FootAsylum">Enjoy 10% Student Discount when you shop with FootAsylum in-store.</string>
    <string name="Oasis">Enjoy 10% Student Discount when you shop with Oasis in-store.</string>



    <!-- Help Page -->
    <string name="aboutUS">Final Year Project application, designed and built by Thomas Fox. The aim is to provide students will
        real time notifications about nearby discounts in their favourite stores.</string>

    <string name="FAQ1_Title">How to view discounts?</string>
    <string name="FAQ1_Description">Go to the menu button in the top left of the screen, and select Discounts.
        From here you can now see and view all discounts available.</string>

    <string name="FAQ2_Title">How to turn off notifications?</string>
    <string name="FAQ2_Description">Select the menu button in the top left and choose settings. From here you can tap the toggle switch to turn off
    notifications for selected categories. There is also the option to turn all notifications off.</string>

    <string name="FAQ3_Title">How to find my location?</string>
    <string name="FAQ3_Description">By going to the map page via the menu, you can select the pointer button that appears in the top right of the screen
    and it will zoom into your location. If you are near any shops with a discount, they will appear with a red pin on them.</string>

</resources>
